[both gasp]
I am the Shadow Beast, Worm.
Which family do you belong to?
[Dalzollene] We’re bodyguards.
We’ve been hired by the Nostrade family.
I understand.
It seems that you can use Nen a bit
but don’t bother.
These are no ordinary thugs
To them, killing’s a part
of their daily routine.
You could say
they’re professional killers.
And as pros ourselves, we’ll handle it.
My name’s Rabid Dog.
And mine is Leech.
You, uh... can call me Porcupine.
Sit back and leave this job
to the Shadow Beasts.
[theme song playing]
BUILDUP x TO A x FIERCE BATTLE
[narrator] After the Phantom Troupe’s raid
on the Underground Auction,
Uvogin has single-handedly
annihilated the Mafia pursuers.
But now they look on
as the Mafia’s secret weapon arrives,
dispatched by the Ten Dons:
The Shadow Beasts.
[mafioso straining]
That was boring.
Not one of ‘em put up much of a fight.
[Shalnark] Uvo!
Yeah?
They’re here now!
[Uvogin chuckles]
[Uvogin] Hey, don’t interfere!
You got that?
I haven’t even had the chance
to enjoy myself.
[Feitan] Oh, boy.
Oh, just let Uvo handle it.
Want in on a round, Feitan?
[Squala] Wait…
is he planning to fight the Shadow Beasts
all by himself?
[Uvogin] The Shadow Beasts, huh?
Where’d you hide the merchandise?
What happened to the guards and guests?
We killed them.
Where’s the merchandise?
If you don’t answer me…
[Worm gasps in shock]
That one stung.
[grunts, rasping in pain]
[grunting]
Huh?
[Worm chuckling]
You can’t escape now.
What’ll it be? Hmm?
Have me kill you underground?
Or would you rather die
at the hands of the other three
up on the surface?
Idiot.
[Feitan] Oh!
Here we go.
Uvo is getting pretty serious.
Four.
You talk a pretty good game.
But can you back it up?
[Worm groans]
BIG BANG IMPACT:
FIST OF DESTRUCTION
[Squala] I-- I don’t believe it!
[Basho] I’ve never seen a Nen user
of this caliber before.
Is that…?
It’s a spider tattoo.
Then, he's...
[loud heartbeat]
[Kurapika's loud heartbeat]
Spiders…
That poor guy.
There’s not much left of him.
[Nobunaga] Uvo’s Big Bang Impact
sure packs a powerful punch.
but to be fair, it’s just a regular punch
with Nen added.
Eight.
[Shizuku] Nine.
[Shalnark] Ten.
Okay. So, who wants to die next?
[Rabid Dog] The Phantom Troupe, huh?
[Porcupine]
Well, he seems pretty confident. Yup.
I think it’s your turn.
Oh, you’re in for it now.
[Uvogin laughs] Nice!
Gotta love reckless opponents!
Easy to kill!
Huh?
I can manipulate my body hair, y’see.
I can even turn it
into these needles if I want to. Yup.
You throw a mean punch,
but it’s pointless
if you can’t connect. Yup.
-[Rabid Dog hisses]
-[Uvogin winces in pain]
[Feitan] They damaged Uvogin’s iron skin
with nothing more
than body hair and teeth.
They must be really skilled Nen users.
I’m impressed, actually!
That’s thirteen.
[Shalnark] No way!
[Shizuku] Sorry.
You want a hand over there, Uvo?
-[Uvogin] Stay out of this!
-[depressed sigh]
Damn it. Come on!
[Porcupine] It’s futile.
There are thousands of needles
in your skin.
You can’t shake them off. Yup.
Then I’ll just have to use you
as an extension of my fist!
Huh?
Since I manipulate it at will,
I can relax sections of my hair
as necessary. Yup-yup yup.
[Uvogin winces in pain]
This is too easy, musclehead!
[Uvogin] That’s bull!
[gasps]
[Rabid Dog] What’s wrong, tough guy?
Finally kick in?
The sensation that you’re feeling
is the fast-acting neurotoxin
my fangs pumped into you.
[Uvogin] Bastard…
[Rabid Dog]
You won’t be affected from the neck up,
so you can still feel fear and pain.
Try and enjoy it.
If he were using lethal poison,
the fight would be all over now.
He probably enjoys torture.
-[slurping noise]
-Hey…
[Leech cackling]
I keep countless leeches
of lots of different sizes
stored within my body.
As we speak,
they’re entering your body
through your injuries
and soon they’ll lay their eggs
in your bladder.
These spotted leeches
are a gift from me to you.
You’re totally disgusting.
You know that?
[Leech cackling]
Most die from the pain.
Hundreds of millions of leeches
hatching inside of your body
is excruciating
as you’re about to find out firsthand.
[Leech cackling]
[grunts of disgust] That’s awful.
I thought that ugly
usually meant better-tasting.
Surprised?
You’re not the only one
who can bite, y’know.
[chuckling]
Even without my body,
my neck and head are more than enough
to beat you.
They will lose.
The Shadow Beasts are dead.
The Shadow Beasts...
are dead.
[Rabid Dog]
You really still think you can win?
No way in hell you can bite me
when I’m all the way over here.
It’s impossible.
[smug chuckle]
A bullet? No.
It’s a chunk he bit out of Leech’s skull!
[focusing grunt]
[dying rasps]
[frightened gasp]
[Porcupine] If he tries that on me,
it’ll never work.
My body hair will deflect
any projectiles, yup.
Huh?
[roaring]
[Kurapika grunts]
You can’t deflect bullets of sound,
can you?
What’s wrong, can’t you hear me?
[Basho] He used sound
to kill a Shadow Beast...
They’re crazy… Completely crazy!
Damn…
Hey, what the hell, you idiot?!
How about a warning next time?
Do you wanna bust our eardrums, too?
[Uvogin] Sorry ‘bout that!
I didn’t want to give away my plan.
Besides, the sound took a while
to reach you guys, didn’t it?
You had plenty of time to cover your ears.
[Machi] That's true.
[Dalzollene] Kurapika, wait!
What are you doing?
[Kurapika] Isn't it obvious?
-I'm going to capture him.
-[Melody, Dalzollene, Squala, Basho] Huh?
That guy?!
No way! You saw what he did!
You’re gonna get yourself killed!
Stop, Kurapika!
It doesn’t matter.
I hear such violent rage and hatred.
He’s gone blind with it!
Kurapika!
[Melody] He’s walking
right into his own funeral.
I have to stop him.
[Dalzollene] Wait just a minute!
[angered growl]
[plays peaceful tune]
[gasps]
[peaceful tune continues]
“Field in Spring”.
The perfect composition for relaxing.
Now, has everyone calmed down?
If so, let’s plan our strategy
with level heads.
Yeah…
What kind of Nen abilities
do the other members possess?
[Squala] I’m willing to bet they’re all
ridiculously strong.
[Kurapika] Melody...
Thanks a lot.
I’ve calmed down.
But I’m still going to capture them.
-Leader.
-Hm?
I stand a good chance.
-[Melody, Squala, Basho, Linssen] Huh?
-What’s that?
Let me do it.
[Dalzollene] You saw
that incredible show of strength
and you still think you have a shot?
I do.
Understood.
We may need to leave quickly,
so please pull the car around.
[Squala] Right.
[Uvogin] Shizuku!
Do me a favor
and suck all the poison and leeches
out of my body!
Your vacuum could do it, right?
Blinky can suck out the poison,
but nothing that’s still alive.
[Uvogin] Really?
Then what do I do?
Let me see.
This is known as a spotted leech.
It takes a nearly a full day for it
to migrate to the bladder
before laying its eggs and dying.
Yeah, then what?
Well, after that,
the eggs will hatch and exit
through your urinary tract.
You’ll most likely die from the pain.
Come on, don’t joke around like that.
However, they require a very specific
concentration of ammonia to hatch.
If there isn't enough,
the eggs stay dormant
and can be excreted harmlessly.
Which means that until this time tomorrow
it’s absolutely critical
that you drink beer constantly
and pee as much as possible!
Is that all? You really had me worried!
Shizuku! Can you get the poison?
[Shizuku] Okay!
[Shalnark] Someone go into town
and get lots of beer.
All right, I’ll go.
And make sure those suckers are ice cold!
[Franklin] You’ll get what I bring you!
[cackling]
Hurry and get this poison out of me!
[gasps]
Huh?
[Uvogin screaming]
-Did you see that?
-Yeah.
Those chains came out of nowhere
and wrapped around his body!
Is it a new Shadow Beast?
Uvo can’t move due to the neurotoxin
and those leeches
are still inside of him, too.
There’s no choice.
We gotta go and save him.
[Feitan] Oh, boy.
So much trouble.
[Machi] We can still find out
where he’s going.
I used In to make my thread invisible.
I can follow them anywhere,
as long as they don’t spot the needle.
And they’d have to use Gyo to do that.
Well? Let’s find them
before they figure it out.
[derisive snort]
Now’s our chance to finish off
the other Shadow Beasts.
[Shalnark] Get as much beer
as you can, Franklin.
[Franklin snorts derisively]
Man, the chase sounds more fun.
[Shalnark laughs]
Come on. Let’s go!
[Worm] Indeed.
The spiders...
[weakly, dying] Listen to me…
Gather up everyone who’s left,
or we...
don't stand a chan--
Understood.
Chains, is it?
[Uvogin] Hey. Driver.
You don’t really think these chains
can hold me, do you?
Kill me now or you’ll regret it.
I promise you that.
Quiet.
Do you hear me?
This is the only chance
you’re ever gonna get.
Stop wasting time and--
[surprised gasp of pain]
[groaning in pain]
I thought I told you to be quiet!
Kurapika! Be careful!
Watch the road!
[Uvogin] Damn… How can he be this strong?
Even if my body wasn’t paralyzed,
I’d still be having trouble.
I don’t know how
but he’s infused these puny chains
with enough Nen to keep me in check.
I’m a master Enhancer.
That shouldn’t even be possible!
Chain Jail…
CHAIN JAIL:
THE RESTRAINING MIDDLE FINGER
...an ability I will use
only on the Spiders.
A power to capture and restrain
the Phantom Troupe.
I’ve sworn to use it for no other purpose.
If I break my vow…
if I should use this technique
on anyone other than a Spider…
my life is forfeit.
I would die...
instantly.
A self-imposed condition
and a contract with myself.
The proof of my resolve.
CONDITION
CONTRACT
[Melody] Kurapika! Look out!
-[Kurapika] The risk is high...
-[Melody] Please, watch the road!
[Kurapika] ...but the greater the strength
of my conviction,
the stronger my Nen!
[narrator] Kurapika has captured
a member of the Phantom Troupe.
Armed with resolve
and the willingness to risk his life,
he prepares for the battle
that will soon begin.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
We’re introducing the Shadow Beasts!
A fighting force for the Mafia’s Ten Dons.
Okay, but who are they?
Owl… then there’s Worm… and Porcupine…
Let me see, now
what was the other one called… Oh, Leech!
[Gon] Next time: “Restraint x and x Vow”!
Killua! Don’t run in the hallway!
[Killua] The Silent Gait
counts as walking.
[Gon] Follow the rules!
Promise me, okay?